<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<se-lint-ignore>
	<file path="a-caddys-diary.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-015">
			<line>168</line>
			<reason>The narrator of this story writes in an idiosyncratic style. Adding the commas to numbers would add enough polish to meaningfully alter his characterization.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="champion.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-029">
			<line>196</line>
			<reason>This letter is written in an idiosyncratic style. Lowercase letters start sentences intentionally.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="mr-and-mrs-fix-it.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-030">
			<line>72</line>
			<line>75</line>
			<line>84</line>
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style by a barely literate narrator. The incorrectly formatted initialisms are intentional</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="nora.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-033">
			<line>76</line>
			<reason>The hyphen is at the end of the line on purpose. It moves the second half of the word to the next line to preserve poetic rhyme and rhythm.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="rhythm.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-007">
			<line>55</line>
			<reason>The name of the newspaper has a possessive, so it belongs in the italics.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="the-battle-of-the-century.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-003">
			<line>63</line>
			<reason>This appears to be a second paragraph from the same speaker. This is grammatically correct.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="the-story-of-a-wonder-man.xhtml">
		<ignore code="s-023">
			<line>340</line>
			<line>365</line>
			<reason>The title of a newspaper is embedded in these chapter titles, and so "The" is uppercase.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="tour-no-2.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-029">
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style. Lowercase letters start sentences and paragraphs intentionally</reason>
		</ignore>
		<ignore code="t-030">
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style by a barely literate narrator. The incorrectly formatted initialisms are intentional</reason>
		</ignore>
		<ignore code="t-057">
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style. Lowercase letters start sentences and paragraphs intentionally</reason>
		</ignore>
		<ignore code="t-064">
			<line>73</line>
			<line>86</line>
			<line>98</line>
			<line>114</line>
			<line>130</line>
			<line>141</line>
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style by a barely literate narrator. The incorrectly capitalization of the ship name is intentional.</reason>
		</ignore>
		<ignore code="y-035">
			<line>20</line>
			<line>88</line>
			<reason>This story is written in an idiosyncratic style by a barely literate narrator. The single letters here are not graphemes or phonemes, just intentionally bad grammar.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="what-of-it.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-017">
			<line>59</line>
			<reason>The question mark is inside the italics tag because the question mark is part of the title of the play.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="women.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-008">
			<line>119</line>
			<reason>The first single quote is an elision character, so having it duplicated is fine here.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
	<file path="zone-of-quiet.xhtml">
		<ignore code="t-017">
			<line>25</line>
			<line>63</line>
			<reason>The question mark is inside the italics tag because the question mark is part of the title of the play.</reason>
		</ignore>
	</file>
</se-lint-ignore>
